So, you don't have a boyfriend now?
で、今って、彼氏とかいないの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Isn't it?
い ないの?
Yeah.
うん
How long have you been gone?
どんくらいいないの?
About half a year.
半年くらい
Haven't you been here for half a year?
半年もいないの?
Yeah.
うん
So what about sex friends?
じゃあセフレとか?
I don't even have a sex friend.
セフレもいないです
Did you hedge at the end?
最後にヘッジしたんですか?
We broke up six months ago, so about six months ago.
別れたのが半年前だから、半年くらい前
Since then, you haven't done it even once today?
そこから今日も、1回もしないの?
Yeah.
うん
I haven't been in a lot of relationships so far,
今まで付き合ってた数ってないんで、
Is that all?
それだけ?
So, do you want to hedge the number of experienced people?
じゃあ、経験人数はヘッジしたり?
Two more people.
もう2人
Are there only two boyfriends?
その彼氏は2人だけ?
Yeah.
うん
My boyfriend has no choice but to finally go?
彼氏やっといっちゃしかない?
No.
ないです
What about hedging?
ヘッジはどう?
Yeah.
うん
Hate hedges?
ヘッジが嫌いか?
like.
好き
How do you like hedges?
どうヘッジが好き?
I like being attacked.
攻められるのが好き
Will it be attacked?
攻められるの?
So, which one would you choose if you became Escha?
じゃあ、エスカになったらどっち?
but,
でも、
Ears or something.
耳 とか
What if I lose my head?
首すっちゃうと?
feeling?
気持ち?
Fall.
落ち
Move your hips around.
腰のキョロキョロして
Are you restless?
落ち着かない?
Yeah.
うん
Which is fierce or gentle?
激しいのと、優しいのと、どっち?
intense.
激しい
Do you prefer intense?
激しいほうが好き?
Yeah.
うん
Do you know what you're saying verbally?
口頭に何語ってるのわかる?
Yeah.
うん
What are you talking about?
何語ってる?
Stand up, feeling.
立ってよ、気持ち
The face, the hardness.
顔、硬さと
Use your tongue and make it feel good.
舌使って、いっぱい気持ちよくして
Will this make me forget to sleep?
これ、自分で寝忘れる?
Did you try to lick it?
お前、舐めようとしたの?
Did you try to lick it without permission?
勝手に舐めようとしたの?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I have to ask.
お願いしないと
Can I lick it?
舐めていいですか?
Wait a minute, try again.
ちょっと待って、もう一回やって
Can I lick it?
舐めてもいいですか?
Can I lick your dick?
ちんちん、舐めてもいいですか?
Is it okay if I make you feel as good as possible?
いっぱい気持ちよくしてくればいいの?
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとうございます
Use the tip of your tongue as much as possible.
い っぱい舌先使って
Just here, without using your hands.
手使わずに、こっちだけで
Can you go back here?
こっちの奥まで帰れる?
To the back of there.
そ っちの奥まで
You can't lick it, right?
舐めちゃダメでしょ?
yes.
はい
Petan are you sitting there?
ペタン座ってるの?
Look here.
こっち見て
Even though it's painful, are you going to keep licking me like that?
苦しいのに、そんな舐めてこやこんじゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
Have you only licked two of my dick?
おじんちの2つしか舐めたことないの?
Yeah.
うん
When you lick it, it's really good.
舐めると、すっごい上手
Want to lick more?
もっと舐めたい?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, come over here.
じゃあ、こっちおいで
You like to lick it.
舐めるのが好きなんだね
I want to lick it.
舐めたい
I'm so crazy again.
またすっごい地狂い
Isn't it crazy already?
もう地狂いとってない?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
I licked it.
舐めちゃった
I'll lick it, I'll do something myself.
舐めるから、自分で何かやるから
I can see something nearby.
近くでも何か見られてる
nostalgic.
懐かしい
nostalgic?
懐かしい?
Yeah.
うん
But, it's shiny.
でもね、テカテカしてるし
Yeah.
うん
Look here.
こっち見て
Let me lick you a lot.
いっぱい舐めらして
Yeah.
うん
Don't you get stronger?
強くされない?
Does it get really hard?
すっごい固くなる?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you get stronger?
強くされない?
Yeah.
うん
You look cute.
かわいい顔してる
It's very flat.
すっごい平体だね
How do you like to be treated?
おもこはどうされるのが好き?
Christmas.
クリスマス
Is it better to breed more?
もっと飼育するほうがいい?
Yeah.
うん
Do you want me to lick you?
舐めてほしい?
I want you to lick me.
舐めてほしい
noisily.
じゃあ、じゃあ
Please lick it.
舐めてください
舐 めてください
So don't worry about this.
じゃあ、これ懸念しないで
Use your hips.
腰使いする
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいかな?
Well then,
じゃあ、
I took it off right away.
す ぐ脱がしまって
Hey!
おい!